Guide to Peter P. Carr Papers RG.055
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
Peter P. Carr Papers
1957-2005
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
RG.055
60 Linear Feet
- Series I: American Options, 1965-2002; 60 Linear Feet
  - An Exact Analytic Formula for the Value of an American Put Option on a Non-Dividend-Paying Stock, 1994-08-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bibliography on American Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Derivatives - A Review, Aase, 1997-12-27; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ahn and Wilmott, On Trading American Options, OCIAM, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ait-Sahlia, F.; Optimal Stopping and Weak Convergence Methods for Some Problems in Financial Economics, 1995-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ait-Sahlia, F.; Corrected Random Walk Approximations for Contingent Claims Problems, Stanford University, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ait-Sahlia and Lai, Approximations for American Options, 1995-12-18; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Albanese, Jaimungal, and Rubisov; Jumping in Line, 2000-07-28; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Amin, Kaushik; Pricing American Options in a Term Structure Economy, Cornell Working Paper, 1988-11-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Amin, K.I. & Bodurtha, J.N.; Discrete-Time Valuation of American Optics with Stochastic Interest Rates, University of Michigan, 1993-07-1995; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Amin/Khanna, Convergence of American Option Values from Discrete to Continuous Time Financial Models, 1992-04; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Andersen and Broadie, A Primal-Dual Simulation Algorithm for Pricing Multi-Dimensional American Options, 2001-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Averbukh, V.; Pricing American Options Using Monte Carlo Simulation, Cornell University Working Paper, 1997; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Avram, F.; A Method for Computing Double Band Policies for Switching Between Two Diffusions, 1996-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Balakrishna, B.S.; Analytic Representations and Approximations to American Option Pricing, UC Boulder Working Paper, 1996-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Barles, Burdeau, Romano, and Samsoen; Critical Stock Price Near Expiration, Mathematical Finance, 1995-04; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Barles, G.; Convergence of Numerical Schemes for Parabolic Equations Arising in Finance Theory, Newton Institute - Cambridge, 1995-04; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Barone-Adesi, Giovanni; American Path-Dependent Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Barone-Adesi, Giovanni; The Free Boundary of American Puts, 1992-04-09; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Baron-Adesi, Free Boundary Problems in the Valuation of Securities, 1989-11-14-1990-04-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - G. Barone-Adesi and M. Chesney, American Path-Dependent Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Barone-Adesi/Elliot, Approximations for the Values of American Options, 1989-10-27; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Barone-Adesi and Elliot, The Valuation of American Options, University of Alberta, 1989-10-05-1990-08-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Baron-Adesi/Whaley, Efficient Analytic Approximation of American Option Values, Journal of Finance, 1987, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Barone-Adesi and Whaley, On the Valuation of American Put Options on Dividend-Paying Stocks, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - J. Barraquand and D. Martineau, Numerical Valuation of High Dimensional Multivariate American Securities, Digital Equipment Corporation, 1994-04; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Basso, Nardon, and Pianca; The Optimal Exercise Boundary of American Options, 2002-03-2002-04-19; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Basso, Nardon, and Pianca; An Analysis of the Effects of Continuous Dividends on the Exercise of American Options, Venice Working Paper, 2002-07-15; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Basso, Nardon, and Pianca; Discrete and Continuous Time Approximations of the Optimal Exercise Boundary of American Options, 2002-03-25; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Bates, D.; Jumps and Stochastic Volatility: Exchange Rate Processes Implicit in Deutsche Mark Options, Review of Financial Studies, 1996; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - A New Look at Optimal Stopping Problems Related, 1997; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Bjerksund and Stensland, Closed-Form Approximation of American Options, Scandinavian Journal of Management, 1993; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Black/Scholes, The Pricing of Options and Corporate Liabilities, Journal of Political Economy, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Bodurtha, Courtadon; The Probability of Early Exercise: Foreign Currency Options and Foreign Currency Futures Options, 1993-01; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Bossaerts, Peter; Simulation Estimators of Optimal Early Exercise, 1989-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Beyarchenko, S.; Pricing of the American Put Under Levy Processes, University of Pennsylvania, 2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Boyle, Phelim; Options: A Monte Carlo Approach, Journal of Financial Economics, 1977; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Green, Richard; The Accelerated Binomial Option Pricing Model, 1991-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Brennan & Schwartz, The Valuation of American Put Options, 1977-05; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Brennan/Schwartz, Finite Difference Methods and Jump Processes Arising in the Pricing of Contingent Claims: A Synthesis, 1978; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Brill/Harriff, Pricing American Options: Managing Risk with Early Exercise, 1986; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Broadie & Detemple, The Valuation of American Options on Multiple Assets, 1994; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Broadie, M. and Detemple, J; American Capped Call Options on Dividend-Paying Assets, 1993-1995; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Broadie & Detemple, American Options on Dividend-Paying Assets, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Broadie, M. and Detemple, J.; American Option Valuation: New Bonds, Approximations, and a Comparison of Existing Methods, 1995; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Broadie, Detemple, Ghysels, & Torres; Nonparametric Estimation of American Options Exercise Boundaries and Call Prices, 1996; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Broadie, Detemple, Ghysels & Torres; American Options with Stochastic Dividends and Volatility: A Nonparametric Investigation, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Broadie & Glasserman, Pricing American-Style Securities Using Simulation, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Broader & Glasserman, A Stochastic Mesh Method for Pricing High-Dimensional American Options, 1997-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Broader & Glasserman, Monte Carlo Methods for Pricing High-Dimensional American Options: An Overview, 1997-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Bunch, D.S. & Johnson, H.; A Simple and Numerically Efficient Method for American Puts Using a Modified Geske-Johnson Approach, 1992-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Bunch & Johnson, The American Put Option and Its Critical Stock Price, 2000-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Cadenillas, Elliott, & Leger; On the Pricing of American Options When the Asset Follows a Mean-Reverting Process, 2002-06-23; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Carr, Elliott, Geman, & Madan; Beyond the American Put, 1997-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Chiarella, El-Hassan & Kucera; Evaluation of American Option Prices in a Path Integral Framework Using Fourier-Hermite Series Expansions, 1997-09; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Chesney & Lefoll, Premature Exercise and American Put Evaluation, 1993-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Carverhill/Webber, American Options: Theory and Numerical Analysis, 1988-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Chang, Chung, & Stapleton; Richardson Extrapolation Techniques for Pricing American-Style Options, 2001-05-21; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Chan, S.; Linear Complementarity and the American Put - A GAMS/PATH Implementation, 1998-09-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Chen & Yeh, Analytical Upper Bounds for American Option Prices, 1999-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Chesney, Marc; Pricing American Currency Options: An Analytical Approach, 1989; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Chesney, Elliott, Gibson; Analytical Solutions to the Pricing of American Bond and Yield Options, 1991-05; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - M. Chesney & R. Gibson, State Space Symmetry and Two Factor Option Pricing Models, IGBF IBFM #9402,1993, 1993-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Clarke & Parrott, The Multigrid Solution of Two-factor American Put Options, 1996-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Clewlow/Carverhill, Efficient Monte Carlo Valuation and Hedging of Contingent Claims, 1992-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Cornwall/Price, The Wise, For Cure, on Exercise Depend; Risk Magazine, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Courtadon, G; A More Accurate Finite Difference Approximation for the Valuation of Options, Journal of Financial and Quantitative Analysis, 1982-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Cox & Rubinstein, Options Markets, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Curran, M.; Accelerating American Option Pricing in Lattices, 1994-12-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Davis, M.H.A. & Zariphopoulou, T.; American Options and Transaction Fees, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Dayanik, Savas; On the Optimal Stopping Problems for One-Dimensional Diffusions with Random Discounting, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Dayanik, S. & Karatzas, I.; On the Optimal Stopping Problem for One-Dimensional Diffusions, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Decamps, J.P. & Rochet, J.C.; A Variational Approach for Pricing Options and Corporate Bonds, 1993-07-19; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Delbaen, F.; The Ratio of American & European Put Options When Time to Maturity is Small, 2000-05; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Dempster & Hutton, Fast Numerical Valuation of American, Exotic and Complex Options; Applied Mathematical Finance, 1997-01; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Dempster & Hutton, Pricing American Stock Options by Linear Programming, 1999-08-24; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Dempster & Richards,Pricing Exotic American Options Fitting the Volatility Smile, 1999-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Detemple, Feng, & Tian; The Valuation of American Options on the Minimum of Two Dividend-Paying Assets, 2001-02-05; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Detemple & Tian, The Valuation of American Options for a Class of Diffusion Processes, 2002-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Dewynne, J. N. & Howison, S.D.; Some Mathematical Results in the Pricing of American Options, European Journal of Applied Mathematics 4, 1993; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Duan & Simonato, American Option Pricing under GARCH by a Markov Chain Approximation, 1997-05; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Karoui, N.E. & Karatzas, I.; The Optimal Stopping Problem for a General American Put-Option, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Evans, Kuske, & Keller; American Options with Dividends Near Expiry, 2000-08-01; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Firoozye, N.; An Explicit Formula for American Puts, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Fischer, E.O.; Analytic Approximation for the Valuation of American Put Options on Stocks with Known Dividends, 1990-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Flamouris, D.V. & Giamouridis, D.G.; "Estimating Implied PDFs from American Options: A New Semi-Parametric Approach", 2000-10-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Forsyth & Vetzal, Quadratic Convergence of a Penalty Method for Valuing American Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Geske & Shastri, Valuation by Approximation: A Comparison of Alternative Option Valuation Techniques, 1985-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Gandhi, Kooros, & Salkin; An Improved Analytic Approximation for American Option Pricing, 1993-03-01; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Garcia, D.; "A Monte Carlo Method for Pricing American Options", 1999-08-1999-09; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - A Monte Carlo Method for Pricing American Options, 2000-08-30; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Garman, M.; Semper Tempus Fugit, Risk Magazine, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Gao, Huang, & Subrahmanyam; An Analytical Approach to the Valuation of American Path-Dependent Options, 1996-07-27; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Gerber & Shiu, Martingale Approach to Pricing Perpetual American Options on Two Stocks, 1996; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Geske, R.; The Valuation of Compound Options, Journal of Financial Economics, 1979; 60 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Geske and Johnson, The American Put Option Valued Analytically, Journal of Finance, Dec '84, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Geske, Robert and Shastri, Kuldeep; The Early Exercise of American Puts, July 1981, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Goldenberg and Schmidt, Estimating the Early Exercise Boundary and Pricing American Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Goodman and Ostrov; On the Early Exercise Boundary of the American Put Option, 2000-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Path-Dependent Options: Extending the Monte Carlo Simulation Approach, Working Paper, 1993-11-30; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Grant, Vora and Weeks; Simulation and the Early-Exercise Option Problem, Journal of Financial Economics, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Gukhal, Chandrasekhar; Efficient Numerical Methods for Pricing American Options, Working Paper, 1996-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Gukhal, Reddy; The Analytical Valuation of American Options on Jump-Diffusion Processes, Columbia Working Paper, 1996; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Gukhal, C.; A General Approach to the Analytical Valuation of American Options, 2001-11-24; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Guo and Zhang, Closed-Form Solutions for Perpetual American Put Options with Regime Switching, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Guth, Michael; Exercise by Numbers, 1992-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Kamrad/Ritchken, "Multinomial Approximating Models for Options with k State Variables", Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Karatzas, Ioannis; Optimization Problems in the Theory of Continuous Trading, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Karatzas, Ioannis; On the Pricing of American Options, Applied Mathematics and Optimization, 1988, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Kelly, D.; Valuing and Hedging American Put Options Using Neural Networks, Carnegie Mellon University Working Paper, 1994-12-15; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Khaliq, Voss, and Kazmi; Valuation of American Options via Penalty Methods, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Kim, In Joon; The Analytic Valuation of American Options on Futures Contracts, 1989-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Kim, In Joon; The Analytic Valuation of American Options, Working Paper S-90-15, 1989-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Kim, J.; Analytic Approximation of the Optimal Exercise Boundaries for American Futures Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Kim, J.; The Analytic Valuation of American Options, Review of Financial Studies, 1990, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Kim, Hongshik; Predicting Early Exercise Premia in American Put Prices, 1994-09-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Kim, Yu; A Simplified Approach to the Valuation of American Options and its Applications, 1993-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Kuske and Keller, Optimal Exercise Boundary for an American Put Option, Applied Mathematical Finance 98, 2001; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Kusuoka, S.; A Remark on American Securities, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Lamberton, D.; Error Estimates for the Binomial Approximation of American Put Options, Annals of Applied Probability, 1998, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Lamberton, Damien; Convergence of the Critical Price in the Approximation of American Options, 4/93, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Lamberton, D.; Brownian Optimal Stopping and Random Walks, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Laurence, Peter; Course on American Options, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Laurence, P.; Bounds for the Price of an American Option on Several Assets: Index and Spread Options, 2001-03-11 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Laurence, Peter; Introduction to the Valuation of American Options: Qualitative Properties, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Laurence, Peter; Bounds for the Price of an American Option on Several Assets: Index and Spread Options, 2001; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Leisen, D.P.J.; The Random-Time Binomial Model, 1997; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Lewis, Alan; Series Solution to the Critical Stock Price, 1995-01; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Little, T.; The Early Exercise Boundary for the American Put-Option as the Solution of a Volterra Equation, 1998-02-17; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Little, Pant & Hou; A New Integral Representation of the Early Exercise Boundary for American Put Options, 2000; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Longstaff & Schwartz, Valuing American Options by Simulation: A Simple Least-Squares Approach, 1998-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Hansen & Jorgensen, Analytical Valuation of American-Style Asian Options, 1997-11-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Hansen & Mussavian, Dual American Option Pricing, 1997-12-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Hansen & Osterby, Accelerating the Crank-Nicolson Method in American Option Pricing, 1998-04-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Hirsa & Madan, Pricing American Options Under Variance Gamma, 2001-08-16; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Ho, Stapleton & Subrahmanyam; A Simple Technique for the Valuation and Hedging of American Options, 1994; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Ho, Stapleton & Subrahmanyam; A Valuation of American Options with Stochastic Interest Rates: A Generalization of the Geske-Johnson Technique, 1996-09-17; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Hoffmann, C.; Valuation of American Options, 2000-10-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Huang & Pang, An MPEC Approach to Inverse Pricing of American Options: The Case of an Implied Volatility Surface, 1999-11-21; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Huang & Pang, Pricing American Options with Transaction Costs by Complementarity Methods, 1999-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Huang & Pang, Option Pricing and Linear Complimentarity, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Ibanez & Zapatero, Monte-Carlo Valuation of American Options Through Computation of the Optimal Exercise Frontier, 1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Ibanez, A.; Valuation of Contingent Claims with Multiple Earlier Exercise Opportunities, 2000-04-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Ingersoll, Jonathan E. Jr.; Approximating American Options and Other Financial Contracts Using "Barrier" Derivatives, 1997-05; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Jacka, S.D.; Optimal Stopping and the American Put, 1991; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Jackel & Rebonato, An Efficient and General Method to Value American-Style Equity and FX Options in the Presence of User-Defined Smiles and Time-Dependent Volatility, 2000-03-27; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Jaillet, Lamberton & Lapeyre; Variational Inequalities and the Pricing of American Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Jamshidian, Farshid; Formulas for American Options, 1989-1990; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Jamshidian, Farshid; An Analysis of American Options, 1993; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Johnson, H.E.; An Analytic Approximation for the American Put Price, 1983; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Jorgensen, P.L.; American Bond Option Pricing in One-Factor Dynamic Term Structure Models, 1997; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Jorgensen, P.; American Option Pricing, 1994-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Joubert & Rogers, Fast, Accurate and Inelegant Valuation of American Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Jourdain & Martini, Yet Another Approximation of the American Put, 1999-12-23; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Jourdan & Martini, American Prices Embedded in European Prices, 1999-11-20; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Ju, Nengjiu; Pricing an American Option by Approximating Its Early Exercise Boundary As a Multi-Piece Exponential Function, 1997; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Ju, Nengjiu; An Efficient and Reliable Approximate Formula for Pricing American Options, 1997; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Ju & Zhong, An Approximate Formula for Pricing American Options, 1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - MacMillan, L.W.; Analytic Approximation for the American Put Option, 1986; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Maini & Fernandes, Successive Over Relaxation Method for American Options, 1995-03-23; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Mane, S.R.; A Fully Explicit Analytic Approximation Formula for Pricing American Options, 1999-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Mane, S.R.; The Early Exercise Boundary of American Options near Expiry, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Mane, S.; Asymptotic Behavior of Early Exercise Boundary, 1999-2000; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Mane, S.R.; A Put-Call Symmetric Analytic Approximation Formula for Pricing American Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Menkveld & Vorst, A Pricing Model for American Options with Stochastic Interest Rates, Erasmus University, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Marcozzi, M.; On the Approximation of Optimal Stopping Problems with Application to Financial Mathematics; University of Nevada, Las Vegas; Working Paper, '99, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Mason, Scott; The Numerical Analysis of Certain Free Boundary Problems Arising in Financial Economics, 1977-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Mastroeni and Matzeu, An Integro-Differential Parabolic Variational Inequality Connected with the Problem of the American Option Pricing, Zeit, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - McDonald and Schroder, A Parity Result for American Options, 1990-11-15; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - McMurray/Yadav, The Early Exercise Premium in American Option Prices Direct Empirical Evidence, 1993-06-18; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Merton, Robert; Theory of Rational Option Pricing, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Meyer, Gunter H.; Front Tracking of Free Boundaries with Curvature Terms, 1991; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Meyer, G.; The Numerical Valuation of Options with Underlying Jumps, Acta Mathematica Universitatis Comenianae, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Meyer and van der Hoek, The Evaluation of American Options with the Method of Lines, 1996; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Myneni, Ravi; The Pricing of the American Option, Stanford Working Paper, 1990-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Myneni, Ravi; The Pricing of the American Option, 1992; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 81)